<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EMedCom_project</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_collection_home">CollectionHome</string>
    <string name="title_activity_charity_home">CharityHome</string>
    <string name="title_activity_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="aboutUs">Reducing medicines waste will improve quality and save resources. There

are a need and an opportunity for strong leadership from pharmacists to help reduce medicines waste.
        Reducing unnecessary dispensing and supply of medicines is an important way of reducing waste. Wasted medicine is everyone’s responsibility
and there are small changes you can make to help reduce the amount of medicine being wasted. When possible, try to make these medicines reusable. It is everyone’s
responsibility.Medical wastes are highly hazardous and put people under risk of fatal diseases. The generation of medical waste has been increasing in quantity and va-
riety, due to the wide acceptance of single-use disposable items. In this project, waste minimization and reusing are practised, thus significant amounts of medical
wastes are to be used. This is a useful project for everyone who would like to donate or even sell their unused medicines to poor people. The collection centre collects
medicine and distributes it to the charity organisations. Often charity organisations can request their needed medicines. Collection centre also exchanges their medicines
between districts.
It includes a huge amount of data being transferred each day, therefore district prediction is included. The main aim is to predict the district where a
particular medicine is most used. It shows which district needs a particular medicine more from the exchange of medicines in between collection centres. The transferred
data is taken as dataset and is cleaned. Now, the feature data is extracted. A set of data is taken for training and testing. Then a suitable model along with cross-
validation is applied to get more accurate results. It uses kNN and decision tree classifier to find the nearest neighbouring clusters. The accuracy is measured and
output is predicted.</string>
</resources>
